# **David Corson**

\*\* Starting a new career as a Software Engineer coming from a Music Engineering background. Due to my lack of professional experience in Software Engineering, I highly recommend viewing projects on my website at <a href="decreation-com">dcorson.com</a>.

5001 SW 20th St.
Apt 5210
Ocala, FL 34474
(937) 414-5106
david.l.corson@gmail.com
dcorson.com

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Freelance Mixing/Mastering Engineer

July 2019 - PRESENT

Working as a freelance mixer/mastering engineer to personal clients for professional releases. During this time I have also worked on a multitude of software engineering projects.

### **Full Sail University**, Orlando, FL — *Lab Specialist*

July 2018 - October 2019

Teaching 4-hour labs on Audio Mixing and Critical Listening in the Recording Arts Department. Reference below.

## **Digital Domain Studios,** Longwood, FL — Assistant Mastering Engineer

January 2018 - July 2018

Working directly under the well-known Mastering Engineer Bob Katz in his personal studio. Reference Below.

### **EDUCATION**

# **Savannah College of Art and Design,** Savannah, GA B.A. - Sound Design and Technology

GRADUATED 2017 - SUMMA CUM LAUDE

Minor: Music Production

### **REFERENCES**

**Bob Katz** - *Mastering Engineer*, Author of 'Mastering Audio' Phone number and reference letter available upon request.

## **Todd Childress** - Department Chair of Recording Arts, Full Sail University

Phone number and reference letter available upon request.

#### **LANGUAGES**

Python, JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, Pug, CSS, SASS/SCSS, C++, SQL, VIM.

### **PACKAGES/MODULES**

WEBDEV: React, Django, Node.js, AWS, Express, Postgresql, REST API, GraphQL, Docker, Git/Github, MikroORM, Anime.js, etc.

*DATA ANALYSIS:* Pandas, Numpy, Matplotlib, Seaborn, Plotly, Selenium, etc.

### **PROJECTS**

**Front End Clone Series:** The front end of three well-known sites: Twitter, Youtube and Gmail, remade from scratch with SCSS and Pug.

Algorithmic Trading Backtester: A python program created for testing years worth of CSV stock prices. Complete with market simulation down to a second level, momentum tracking, and so much more.

**Sorting Visualizer:** JavaScript-based site for showcasing the logic behind popular sorting algorithms like Quick-Sort or Merge-Sort. Complete with smooth color-coded animations of the sorting process.

**Interactive Pathfinder:** JavaScript-based site animating and explaining the logic behind popular pathfinding algorithms such as Dijkstra's and A\*.